

Passionate Full Stack & Blockchain Developer offering 8+ years of relevant exp erience in Blockchain, ML and Robotic. I have experience developing DeFi, DEX, DApp, Trading Bot, Token, autonomous systems and artificial intelligence. I a m fluent in Solidity, Web3.js, Python and JavaScript, and have worked on a vari ety of projects as a project manager, helping clients achieve their goals. I am al so keen on several JavaScript and Python web frameworks like Vue, React, Dja ngo and Flask I am a life-long learner and is looking forward to working on exci ting and challenging projects. I am continuously trying to improve, learn more and gain new experiences. With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team setting. Looking for a Blockchain Developer job within a forward-moving company.

### MARKO PETROVIC (Blockchain Engineer)

#### Location:

Obrenobac, Serbia

### E-Mail:

babybear88yy@gmail.com

### Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/markopetrovic-5a289720a/

### Skype:

live:.cid.ad5849b44a8a7257

### Telegram:

@nftgoldhat

### **Hobbies**

- Market Researching
- Gaming
- Sprots

### Languages

English - Intermediate

Chinese - Intermediate

### **Education**

April 2006 – March 2012

**Bachelor of Science: Computer Information Systems - Macau University** 

### **Skills**

Fast Learner	Solidity
Hard worker	Ether.js
Computer Skills	Javascript
Team Player	Web3.Js
Excellent Communication Skills	Chart Bot
Leadership and Teamwork	React
Good time management skills	Next
Always on time	Redux
Flexible schedule	Python
Tailwind CSS	Typescript
Responsive UI	Rust

# **Employment History**

# Senior Blockchain Developer, Vision. Exchange (fully Remote)

#### NOVEMBER 2021 — JANUARY 2022

- VZN, LSD token deployed on Binance, Ethereum, Polygon, Cronos, Solana mainnet
- Vzn.exchange website UX/UI design and deployment
- Presale contract, IDO
- Crosschain(10 chains such as Binance, Ethereum, Polygon, Cronos and et c) bridge smartcontracts
- Crosschain Swap/Liquidity/Farming/Staking smartcontracts
- Crosschain NFT Marketplace(Genesis NFT)
- Crosschain NFT Game(Genesis NFT)

# Senior Blockchain Developer, Polarsync (fully Remote)

#### JANUARY 2020 — NOVEMBER 2021

- Trading bot with strong strategies (Front running, snipping, arbitrage, contract bot)
- NFT marketplace with Smart UI and high-end functionalities in Ethereum,
   Binance, Cardano, Solana, etc
- DEX and Centralized Crypto Exchange
- Advanced Trading Platform (Stocks, CFD, Forex, Option, Features...)
- Portfolio Tracking Platform
- Multichain Web and Mobile Wallet
- Crypto Betting and Casino
- Yield Farming Protocols
- Automated Market Making (AMM) Protocols
- Flash Loans
- Impermanent loss, governance tokens
- P2P/Pool Lending and Borrowing
- Crypto Collectible Platforms and Non-Fungible Tokens
- Custom dApps
- NFT Game Development
- ERC20, ERC777, ERC223, ERC721, ERC1155 Smart Contract Development
- Token Design Stable Coins, Utility, Security, Investment, Dividend
- coins.

# Senior Python Developer, Ebunch (fully Remote)

#### JULY 2019 — JANUARY 2020

- Supported large enterprise customers by implementing and deploying mi ssion-critical chat-bots built with Rasa. Deployments use Docker, Docker C ompose, Kubernetes, and OpenShift. Infrastructure a combination of onprem, AWS, GCP, and Azure.
- Designed and implemented NLU data, dialog stories, rules, forms, and cus tom actions (Python) for industry-relevant demonstrator chat-bots.
- Extended Rasa Open Source (Python) available at https://github.com/rasa HQ/rasa. This is an open-source machine learning framework to automat e text- and voice-based conversations: NLU, dialogue management, conn ect to Slack, Facebook, and more.
- Created and taught an online course on advanced deployment technique s with Kubernetes (https://www.udemy.com/course/rasaadvanced-deplo yment-workshop/).
- Implemented Python Asyncio in back-end APIs resulting in dramatically i mproved throughput rates.
- Created CI/CD pipeline that trains a Rasa bot, builds a custom docker ima ge, stores the artifacts in AWS S3 and AWS ECR, automatically creates an AWS EKS cluster using the eksctl CLI, deploys Rasa with Helm, and Smoke Tests using Python.

### Senior Python Developer, Mazama Media (fully Remote)

#### JANUARY 2019 — JULY 2019

- Developed ML models for NLP, including methods for domain adaptation, methods for automated feature selection, methods for optimization of Fmeasure. Applied models such as logistic regression, SVM, CRF for both cl assification and sequence tagging.
- Developed a machine learning model for classification of tweets as either rumor/not rumor in R.
- Acquired in-depth knowledge in relational databases, ontologies, and link ed data. Implemented a classification model written in Java, that automat ically categorizes Wikipedia pages as either belonging to the topic "Food and Drink" or not.
- Experimented with topic models with LDA in order to help with a recomm ender system for a large publishing company.
- Built prototypes for training word-vectors embeddings and graph embed dings.
- Developed models for sentiment analysis for English and Bulgarian, in R a nd Java. The methods were supervised for English and unsupervised for B ulgarian.

Acquired significant experience with automated and semi-automated integration of various RDF resources as DBpedia and Geonames.

# Senior Blockchain Engineer, MY2BE (fully Remote)

#### IANUARY 2017 — DECEMBER 2018

- Interfaced with several crypto-exchange APIs like KuCoin, Binance, Bittre x, Bitfinex, OKEx, Poloniex, Huobi, and CCXT.
- Used REST APIs and WebSocket APIs.
- Saved time-sensitive data into a Redis database and provided database cli ents to retrieve data through a simple interface.
- Developed asyncio implementations for asynchronous operations.
- Used cfscrape (a Python library) to bypass a Cloudflare anti-bot page

# Senior Software Developer, FIXER Inc. (fully Remote)

#### JANUARY 2015 — DECEMBER 2016

- Built a web-based intranet application to streamline the process of mana ging in-house training data within the organization.
- Worked closely with the project champion, stakeholders, and users to lea
  rn the business workflow and identify the pain points that could be eased
  with automation.

## Senior Software Engineer, UPWORK (fully Remote)

#### JANUARY 2012 — MAY 2020

- Implemented features for the main site and internal applications using Ty peScript, React, Redux, Python and SQLAlchemy.
- Improved and upgraded the development tooling and workflow for sever al projects (TypeScript & Python).
- Coordinated the scrum process and helped improve communication within and between teams as scrum master for two teams.
- Developed a blockchain explorer and cryptocurrency accounting system f or Bitcoin and Ethereum.
- Implemented a method for efficiently tracking the flow of funds between different addresses.
- Deployed the system on DigitalOcean using Docker